

Vo Thi Cam Nhung

CONTACT INFORMATION -

- ☐ October 18, 1995
- □ Female
- 0983114763
- □ vothicamnhung1995@gmail.com
- ☐ Cao Lanh City, Dong Thap

OBJECTIVE -

Hope to apply the experience in sales skills, products introduction as well as combining with specialized knowledge in 5 years with the skills and strengths of myself to become a good Medical Representative. And can bring more value to customers, connect between the company and customers. At the same time, I'm looking forward to learning more things in the professional, dynamic working environment of the multinational company to improve myself and accumulate much experience for future promote.

SKILLS -

English skills and computer skills

Computer skills

Communication skills

Teamwork skills

Working under high pressure

Sales and introduce products

Planning skills, problem solving skills

Presentation, persuasion skills

EDUCATION -

Oct 2013 - present

Can Tho University of Medicine and Pharmacy

Major: Pharmacy GPA: 8.65/10

Will graduate in June 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2014 - March 2017

Hoa Nong Lua Vang Company

Seasonal sales staff

Main responsibilities:

- Introduce products and answer customers' queries.
- Synthesize opinions, needs, tastes of customers.
- Make sales report every day.

April 2017 - August 2017

An Giang Plant Protection Joint Stock Company

Part-time Sales Staff

- Introduce products.

Achievements and skills gained:

- More active.
- Observe, learn and catch customers' taste well.
- Improve communication skill.

ACTIVITIES —

November 2013 - February 2018

Dong Thap Students Association

Core member

- Planning events every semester.

November 2013 - August 2017

Youth Volunteer Team atuniversity

Core member

- Planning events every month.

2014 - present

Green Summer Volunteer Campaign

Volunteer

- Tutoring for disadvantaged children.

2014 - 2015

Pharmacy Youth Union Executive Committe Member

- Management.
- Plan extra-curricular activities for Pharmacy students

Achievements and skills gained:

- Communication skill and Leadership.
- Learn how to organize social events.

INTERESTS

Travelling

Joining in social activities

Singing, reading book

Playing chess and badminton

CERTIFICATIONS

English Certificate level B

Computer Certificate level A

HONORS & AWARDS

Received Excellent Student award for 4 consecutive years

Received Student of 5 merits award for 4 consecutive years

Received encouraging Scholarship in 9 consecutive semesters

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Sense of responsibility, carefulness in all the works done are my greatest strengths.
- Positive, motivated and hard- working person who is keep on working and contributing.
- Willing to join in any training courses to get better to contribute more.
- Proactive to work in team or individually to complete all tasks given.